Raphael Larrinaga, ux & ui & front end

I work for agencies as a front end dev with a background of a ux & ui designer. I also like to take care of full website creation or redesign for direct customers. I worked on a bunch of Drupal websites since 2012. I like simple and usable interfaces. I work remotely.

Education

Since 2012

Frontend United 2013, 2017, 2018

Drupal Camp 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017

June 2011

Haute École Albert Jacquard -Namur

Bachelor's degree in Computer Graphics - Web Design & Multimedia

Tools

Code GIT, VSCode, Sublime text,
iTerm, Fractal, Lando, Vagrant,
Virtualbox

Ux/Ui Sketch, Adobe Ps Ai Xd,
Bootstrap, GA/tag manager, Pen &
paper

Interests

Food, Nature, SciFi, Architecture, Cycling, Sport

Languages

French Mother language

Spanish Father language

English Good written/spoken, technical

https://raphael-larrinaga.be/

https://www.drupal.org/u/raphael-larrinaga

https://www.linkedin.com/in/raphael-larrinaga-252935117

https://twitter.com/RaphLarrinaga

Experience

09/2020 - now

Freelance

Front end, Drupal theming & site building

02/2019 - 09/2020

Walking Men - Digital design agency

Front end development

11/2011 - 01/2019

Tilt Factory - Communication agency

Front end development, web design, Drupal theming

01/2011 - 03/2011

Central Design - UX/UI agency

Web design, front end integration (intern)

Skills

Frontend Dev HTML, CSS/SCSS, BEM, SMACSS, JS (ES5, ES6, React), PHP, Gulp, Bash, Living styleguide, Mailing

Ux/Ui design IA, Wireframing,
Prototyping, Personas, Interface
design, Ergonomics, Icon design

Drupal D8, D7, Drush, Composer, Twig, YML, Theming, Site building, Modules dev, Maintenance



Born in 1988

0485/990.961

Living in Brussels

raphael.larrinaga@gmail.com

Belgian